frontrowed.com 2017-09-19

# Privacy

The following is our privacy policy. It discusses the high degree of importance that we place on your Privacy, and also the rules and conditions related to privacy of information while using our service.

## 1.0 Our Privacy Pledge

At Front Row Education, Inc. (“Front Row”), we are committed to providing a safe and secure learning experience for students, educators, and parents who use our websites, services, and software (collectively, our “Application”). We want you to know that your trust is key to the success of our business. We take privacy and confidentiality very seriously and we safeguard the personal information of our users in accordance with this Policy. In this Policy “personal information” means personal information about an identifiable individual, but excludes business contact information; and “Services” means services provided by Front Row through the Application or desktop interface.

## 1.1 Consent

By using our Services and supplying information to us, or by using the Front Row Application, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information by us for the purpose of providing Services to you via the Front Row Application, and administering your account in accordance with: (a) this Policy, (b) any other agreement you may have entered into with us, and (c) applicable laws and regulations. It is your responsibility to ensure that we are kept informed of the correct and current contact information for you.

## 1.2 Collection of User Information

Front Row collects limited personal information from administrative personnel at the school board, educational institution or teachers who have contracted with Front Row, only as needed for the operation and management of the educational Services provided by Front Row.

## 1.3 Collection of Student Information

Front Row collects limited personal information from minor students, only as needed for the operation and management of the educational Services provided by Front Row, and only where that student’s school board, educational institution or teacher has contracted with Front Row to do so. We first require the school board, educational institution or teacher to obtain the consent of parents/legal guardians prior to collecting such information. If you are a minor student, do not send any personal information about yourself or other students to Front Row, other than what is requested upon signing up for the Services. In the event that we discover we have the personal information of a student without consent of a parent/legal guardian, or information in excess of what we request upon sign-up, we will permanently destroy that information as quickly as possible. If you believe a student may have provided us personal information without consent of a parent/legal guardian, or information in excess of what we request upon sign-up, please contact us at support@frontrowed.com . Students who have signed up with an access code provided by a school or teacher should be aware that their parent/legal guardian has access to all information within or associated with their Front Row account, including, but not limited to, messages between other students, teachers, and assignment grades. All teachers within a single course group in the password-protected portion of the Front Row site have the ability to view student profiles, but visibility is limited to such information as their names and scores. Students are unable to see the grades of other students, irrespective of whether or not they are members of the same course group on the site. If a school or district requests deletion of students’ personal information under the control of the school or district, please contact us at support @frontrowed.com and we will permanently destroy that information as quickly as practicable.

## 1.4 Information of Others

By inputting any personal information into the Application (including the personal information of others), you consent to the use of that personal information within the Application, and you represent and warrant that you have obtained any permissions or authorizations for any personal information of others that you input or send through the Application.

## 1.5 Communication

You authorize us to communicate with you regarding our services and your account. You authorize us to communicate with you via the internet and via the email address you have provided. You understand and accept the risk that data and information transmitted over the internet is susceptible to error or security breaches.

## 1.6 Information Use & Sharing

We do not share, trade, sell or in any way disclose your personal information without your consent unless such a disclosure is: (a) required by law; (b) mandated by search warrant or court order; or (c) warranted during investigation of the commission of an offence, a breach of a contract, or breach of a law or regulation. We may collect, aggregate and anonymize data for system monitoring, quality control and product improvement purposes, provided it does not collect, use or disclose any personal information. We do not rent or sell information for marketing purposes.

## 1.7 Information Security

Front Row Education maintains strict administrative, technical and physical procedures to protect information stored in our servers, which are located in the United States. Access to information is limited (through user/password credentials) to those employees who require it to perform their job functions. We use industry-standard Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology to safeguard the account registration process and sign-up information. Other security safeguards include but are not limited to data encryption, firewalls, and physical access controls to building and files.

## 1.8 Dispute Resolution

In the event you have a question, complaint or dispute regarding your personal information or our personal information handling practices, contact us at support@frontrowed.com

## 1.9 Business Transfers

As a corporate entity, Front Row may elect to buy or sell assets. These transactions normally entail the transferring of user information as a business asset. In such an event any acquirer of Front Row may continue to use personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

## 2.0 Changes to our Privacy Policy

Front Row may modify or update this Privacy Policy from time to time so you should review this page periodically. If we change the policy in a material manner, for example if we seek to use personal information in a materially different way than we had previously, we will provide at least 30 days notice to schools so that you have sufficient time to evaluate the change in practice. Of course, you can always opt-out by deleting your account before the changes take effect.

Effective Date: July 24, 2017
